但他必须以跑至生命的尽头为代价 这就一文不值了
He would have to run until he died,making them worthless.
我解了咒 让这鞋值
I remove the curse, making them worth, like,
说不好 800万美元
I don't know, 8 million dollars?
奥林匹克见
See you at the olympics.
这个有诡异智力的玩偶会威胁要杀死带走它的那家人
This eerily intelligent doll was theratening to murder its family.
现在 它可以为他们处理税务
Now, it does their taxes.
一切皆可减免
Everything's deductible.
再不需要出卖灵魂来换取好东西
Don't pay for the cool stuff with your soul,
付钱就成
pay for it with money.
就像这世界里其他的商店一样
You konw, like how every other store in the world works.
本店坐落在老城第一主干道
We're located at first and main in old town.
赶紧行动 机不可失
Come on, come on down.
第一主...
"First and..."
免费的邪物也在这个地方
Where you can get evil items for free!